Li Ka Lok

I worked as a data analyst for a year in 2022. Since then, I have assisted my mom to take care of my nephew and learnt web development & CS concepts like data structure and algorithms.

9149 8950 likalok96@gmail.com Personal website github

EXPERIENCE

DataTech.ai — Data Analyst

Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

- Built dashboard using Tableau and Python
- Used data model to calculate customer churn probability
- Assisted in data preparation and cleaning for building ML models

Legal Aid Department — Statistical Assistant

Noc 2019 - Nov 2020

- Assisted in data preparation and entry
- Assisted in data analysis and provide information needed for reporting

EDUCATION

The Open University of Hong Kong — Bachelor of Science with Honors in Statistical Analysis and Data Science

Sep 2017 - Jul 2019

The Hong Kong Polytechnic University — HD in Applied Physics

Sep 2014 - Jul 2017

PROJECTS

WNP Shop — wnp-ecom.com

WNP SHOP is a clone website from Whiskers N Paws ecommerce website. Frontend is built with React. Backend is built with Nodejs, Express, MySQL, JWT for authentication and Stripe for payment.

LOL Draft — <u>likalok96.github.io/lol_draft/</u>

LOL Draft is a LoL draft simulator. It is built with React and Firestore.

AVAILABILITY

Immediate available

Expected Salary

\$ 18,000 - 20,000

SKILLS

HTML

CSS Javascript React Nodejs Python SQL Git

LANGUAGES

Cantonese, English